<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Immigra</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Immigra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>John Guirguis</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:13:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Core Motivations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/post/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/post/motivation/</guid>
      <description>As a child or immigrants and an immigrant myself I was always intimately aware of my family&amp;rsquo;s desires to be fully fledged citizens of the country we now call home. But as I came to realize the process by which one becomes either a citizen or a naturalized citizen is an extraordinarily complex process that takes an extremely long time. And it is often times the bueracracy and paperwork involved in these processes that contributes to these long wait times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difficulties Immigrants Face</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/post/immigrationarticle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/post/immigrationarticle/</guid>
      <description>In a recent article in migrationpolicy.org the following issues were found with the immigration application process.&#xA;The U.S. immigration system, long criticized for its reliance on outdated paper processes and persistent backlogs, has undergone subtle yet significant changes to adapt to the demands of the 21st century, with the COVID-19 pandemic serving as a catalyst. Embracing high-tech solutions and streamlined operations, including increased online application options, remote hearings, extended document validity periods, and interview waivers, has resulted in faster processing of visas, improved access to work permits, and record numbers of cases resolved in immigration courts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/about/</guid>
      <description>About Us Made with ❤️ by John Guirguis with the integral help of Hugo Bootstrap Theme team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.&#xA;We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Hey everyone my name is John Guirguis, a senior at the University of Pennsylvania studying biology and computer sciene. If you would like to see some of my other projects check out my Github!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy TLDR: We do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data.&#xA;Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for The server hosting this site can collect the following information:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sobre</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/about.pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugo-mock-landing-page/about.pt/</guid>
      <description>Sobre nós Feito com ❤️ pela equipa Hugo Bootstrap Theme.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
